https://www.eqdepot.com/privacy-policy

COVID-19 UPDATE: Supporting essential businesses. Prioritizing your safety and health. | Click here for more information.&Cross
COVID-19 UPDATE: Click here.&Cross
BLOGCUSTOMER LOGINLOCATIONS888.EQDEPOTCONTACT USRENTRENT NOW,
change zip codeSEARCH EQUIPMENTFIND LOCATIONEXISTING CUSTOMER?SIGN INRENTAll Equipment RentalsForklift RentalsScissor Lift RentalsBoom Lift RentalsTelehandler RentalsHigh Capacity Forklift RentalsBUYSEARCH USED.BUY SATISFIED.Our extensive Used inventory — just a click away.SEARCH NOWBUYUsed EquipmentFORKLIFTS  |  REACH TRUCKS  |  PALLET JACKSSCISSOR LIFTS  |  BOOMS  |  TELEHANDLERSBIG FORKLIFTS | CONTAINER HANDLERS | PORT CRANESUtility Vehicles | Tow Tractors | Floor ScrubbersWarehouse Supplies CatalogAgriculture EquipmentFinancingWAREHOUSE SOLUTIONSPROBLEM:SKILLED LABOR SHORTAGE.SOLUTION:AUTOMATED EQUIPMENT FLEET.SEE MORESOLUTIONSWAREHOUSE SOLUTIONSEQ SolutionsWarehouse Design & PlanningWarehouse RackingConveyor Systems & SortationWarehouse AutomationAutomated Guided Vehicles (AGVs)Automated Storage & Retrieval Systems (AS/RS)Semi-Automated Equipment & SystemsWarehouse EquipmentSERVICE & PARTSSERVICE & PARTSPartsServiceTrainingSafetyBatteries & ChargersNATIONAL SUPPORTNATIONAL SUPPORTNational AccountsFleet ManagementFinancingLocationsWHY USWHY USReinventing an IndustryPerformance. Guaranteed.Customer CXperienceCustomer ReviewsIndustry RecognitionNews & PressLeadershipResources888.EQDEPOTLOCATIONSCUSTOMER LOGINBLOG
PRIVACY POLICY
PRIVACY POLICY
Our Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect:
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Equipment Depot website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages may include:
Name Address Email address Phone number Credit/Debit Card Information
The Way We Use Information:
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses not shared with outside parties. From time to time we collect email addresses from email inquiries to add to our sales newsletters.
You can register with our website if you would like to receive our catalog as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment To Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy:
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting making corrections.
How To Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 888.EQDEPOT or send us an email at marketing@eqdepot.com.
REQUEST MORE INFORMATION
Thank you for contacting us. We look forward to assisting with your material handling and equipment rental needs.
Your message has been sent.
THANK YOU FOR CONTACTING US
Thank you for requesting a free quote. We look forward to assisting you with your rental needs.
THANK YOU FOR CONTACTING US
Thank you for requesting a free quote. We look forward to assisting you with your material handling needs.
REQUEST MORE INFORMATION
We look forward to assisting with your material handling and equipment needs. Please complete the form below so we can better serve you.
NOTE: For accounting, HR, and general inquiries, please visit our Contact Us page.
